For the rest of the pirates of the world,
this has proven to be the end of the road,
a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber
after eating the gum gum fruit,
sets sail into the new world with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
The first stop on Luffy's journey to the new world
is Fishman Island.
Thousands of feet below sea level,
where his crew becomes involved in a civil war.
Meeting Jinbei in the sea forest,
they learn of the events that led to the conflict.
He tells the tale of the Fishman pilots,
the island's brave queen,
and its hero, Fisher Tiger.
Back to the present.
Horty makes a move.
hunt' hours.
には
フローマン
エ Whoops!
shipping
には
が
犯人が
唯一の猫に
ない死
に
残り
Wait, Jinbei!
What kind of scum would assassinate our queen?
Spread out and find them!
Turn the island upside down if you have to!
First brother Tai, now Queen Otohime!
I can't! I can't!
How am I supposed to live with this anger?
What piece could I ever hope to find?
No, damn it!
There he is! The shooter's up there!
Go! Get to the rooftop!
Is he the one?
I saw him with a gun in his hand. There's no doubt.
Where is the car?
Boss Jinbei! One of our men just killed him, sir.
Was it someone we know?
Far from it.
It can't be!
It's a human!
Hide the body!
Hold on. Do what?
If this gets out, it'll ruin everything the queen has accomplished.
All of her work will be for nothing.
She'll never be able to rest in peace!
Maybe. But that still doesn't change the truth, does it?
The truth is that he was a lawless pirate.
Pirate or no pirate, all that matters is he was human.
Huh?
Leave it be, Horny!
Don't do it, damn you!
Listen, everyone!
It was a human!
A human assassinated our queen!
This is what humans are capable of!
Killing and co-blood!
She trusted them with all her heart!
A human?
All she ever wanted was a peaceful coexistence.
And this human murders her just when she finally had us convinced.
We put all of our faith in her.
And he's stolen that from us by taking Queen Otehime's life.
He's taken our hearts and the future of this country.
We could kill you a million times and never replace our queen, you human!
Is there no justice in the world?
What joy can we find now?
It's more than I can take!
All I can see is despair.
All I can see is regret.
Has the king agreed to leave the tower yet?
Afraid not.
There's no reasoning with him.
He's so stricken with grief and rage, he's lost all control.
King Neptune!
Lock the door behind me and leave it shut until my urge to kill has subsided!
King Neptune, will you talk to me?
Hmm?
I'm listening.
The shooter was discovered with the gun still in his hand, so one of our soldiers killed him.
He was a human.
I would have torn off his limbs whether he were armed or not.
but my queen would never have allowed such savagery
i don't even know when this all began but i would only perpetuate it further by seeking revenge
if the children of our nation were to see me engage in such acts it would only teach them
bitterness show them that rage is the answer and this horrible bloodshed would spiral onward
it was easy to empathize with otohime's message of peace so long as it was someone else's problem
but now why would it be wrong for me to kill the man who shot my wife to death
why is that not my right as much as i want to i just can't understand that
in my time as a soldier i took many lives in reprisal from my fallen comrades
and i've killed swarms of humans over the years who besieged us
but my hypocrisy kept me from helping otohime and her endeavors
so i simply stood by her side and watched
why should she die while a beast like me is allowed to live
i could never take over her work because my hands are forever stained with the blood of my brutal history
my king we're all teeming with contradictions and we all change with age
that goes for fish men and humans alike
but there are some things that only a soldier can have the strength to understand
king neptune
thank you for helping me i'm not certain if i'm ready but
at least i can attend my wife's funeral
father you made it i've missed you so much
she's a hoshi
father
my brave sons
welcome back
i'm sorry children i shouldn't have left you alone during such a terrible time
you should see this father
hmm
what is it
these letters keep flying after me no matter where i go
she's already received five of them father
is this
a love letter
shira hos is only six years old
who in blazes is this vander deccan
that's the name of a legendary pirate isn't it sire
my children will not attend the funeral
there could be an accomplice still on the loose for all we know
also i want this sleazy deccan character apprehended post haste
yes sir
oh
My kingdom.
Look up there.
Prince Fukuboshi.
Then he isn't here?
Fukuboshi.
To all my fellow fishmen.
I'm sorry to interrupt my mother's funeral, but there's something I need to tell you.
So I ask that you please forgive me and lend me your full attention.
In her last moment of life, my mother happily spoke to us of the future.
She told us that we are almost there.
Our new home in the light of the sun.
We have chosen to adopt our mother's dream and dedicate our lives to seeing it through,
no matter how long it takes.
So noble.
We understand that you are not yet ready, and you likely won't be, for the World Summit in two years.
But there will be another in six years, and another after that in ten.
It's only natural for this tragedy to have reaffirmed your deeply held mistrust of humans.
So I'll destroy the remaining signatures that were left unburned.
And together, we'll start from the beginning.
Someday in our future, when your wounds have finally begun to heal,
once you feel you are ready,
united, we will dream of a new life in the sun.
In the decade that followed,
the remaining members of the royal family, including the king himself,
rarely left the palace, but chose to speak to the nation through their monitors instead.
And all the while, the islander's signature steadily replenished.
So there you have it.
That's how we spent the past 16 years fighting discrimination.
And that's how the Fishman Pirates were formed.
And divided.
There's no denying the awful things Arlong did to your home.
Even so, at one time, he was like a brother to me.
When we received news of his violent actions,
we took it upon ourselves to stop him.
But he always managed to dodge any real consequence.
He hid his actions from the Navy by bribing any soldiers that he came across.
I let him live, and in failing to stop him,
I too share the guilt for his crimes.
And that's why, though it pains me, it's my fault.
Oh yeah?
If you're so sorry, kill yourself.
Sanji!
Take responsibility.
Pay with your life for the suffering that you caused her.
Give her peace.
That's enough, Sanji.
What?
Are you serious, Nami?
How could you excuse the things they did to you?
I'll never excuse what Arlong did.
But Jinbei?
He never meant for anyone to get hurt.
Wait.
Are you sure?
I will accept any punishment.
If you wish for me to take my own life...
Drop it.
Look, it's okay.
The only one I hate is Arlong.
Believe me, I'm relieved to hear you're not the mastermind of the Arlong Pirates.
And you're a friend of Luffy's, which tells me plenty about you.
I won't lie.
The Arlong Pirates made my life a living hell.
But you know, if it wasn't for that nightmare, I never would have met my friends.
That awful time made me who I am.
I can't hate you just because you're a fish man.
So you...
You don't get to pity me just because of my past.
I'm fine with my past.
Because I'm happy in the present.
It doesn't matter who did this to me.
Don't become angry.
Not on my behalf.
Please, you can't tell anyone on the island.
The tragedy that we've endured.
And our hatred must die with us.
I wouldn't dwell on it.
There's nothing you could have done.
You've known each other since childhood, after all.
Like him or not, he's still like a brother to you.
And you're no killer.
I don't deserve to be treated so kindly.
You have my gratitude.
Nami!
You're a good man, Jinpei.
I know how hard it is to be a big brother.
You're a hell of a guy, Jinpei.
That whole story.
I like them all so much.
Tiger and Odashime and what's his name?
Shut your mouth, Frankie!
He must have been carrying so much pain.
Huh?
Luffy?
What?
Moron!
Wake up!
I needed that nap.
I should have known.
The only time you can sit still is if you're asleep.
Huh?
Jinbei, are you crying?
Oh, come now.
Of course I'm not crying.
What did I miss?
It's nothing, all right?
Let's forget it.
Move on.
Hmm.
Sure.
Whatever.
So, Jinbei, what did the queen end up doing to that thief she got?
Are you for real?
You mean you fell asleep at the very beginning of the story?
Did I miss it all?
You did!
Shirohoshi, right?
You gonna be okay?
Namichin!
She's royalty!
Don't be so casual, please!
Oh, forgive me for being so emotional.
It's difficult not to cry when I think about my mother.
She sounds like she was quite the woman.
Yes.
It's a real pleasure to meet you, Namichin.
No, princess.
Namichin is just a silly nickname I gave her, so it's just plain Nami.
No, Jin!
Excuse me.
Perhaps it's a bit forward of me to say this,
but even though we just met, I feel a connection to you.
Like we've been friends for a long time.
Oh, yeah?
Well, we've both been through some similar rough patches.
Excuse me.
I just lost track of time.
I need to know what the situation is at the Ryugu Palace.
Just to confirm what you've told me,
Horty and his crew have taken the king and the palace guards captive.
Apart from that, you're not sure what happened to three members of your crew.
And that's all the information we have, correct?
You...
Hey, Jinbei!
If the siege is playing out as Horty planned,
there's a good chance the rest of the country is falling to his forces now, too.
Hold on.
Are you saying you know what his plan is?
To be honest, I have had my suspicions he was up to something ever since he retired from the army.
But he was clever enough to keep the details hidden from me.
Not me.
I know.
But first, let me warn you.
Horty hates humans even more than Arlong did.
The only thing driving him is resentment.
He talks about rebuilding the kingdom, but all he really wants to do is cause suffering to humans.
And to prove my point, you'll see there's one big difference between him and Arlong.
Arlong had no problem with killing humans, but the one thing he'd never do is hurt other fishmen.
Horty, he doesn't care.
He'll also turn his fury against fishmen who are sympathetic to humans.
He'll cut down anyone in his way.
The World Summit is set to take place again soon, but a lot's changed in the last four years.
For the first time since Odohime's death, they've actually gathered enough signatures for King Neptune to speak at the summit about relocating Fishman Island to the surface.
Hmm. I see.
Then Horty has seized the palace just for that?
I wish.
No, I'm afraid it's a lot worse than that.
Ah!
What? What is that?
It's huge! They get that big?
What the? It's a video transponder snail. What's it doing out here?
Look! It's activated!
Oh yeah, it's projecting! On the bubble!
Ah!
Hmm. I thought so.
It's him.
What's up?
You know that guy?
That's Horty.
This can't be good.
He found us?
Hodgins!
Hello there, people of Fishman Island.
Am I coming through?
Well then, for those of you who don't know, I'm the captain of the new Fishman Pirates.
My name is Horty Jones!
I'm the captain of the new Fishman Pirates.
Broadcasting across all of Fishman Island, Horty makes his plans for conquest clear.
The people watch in horror as he prepares for Neptune's execution.
Those who would oppose him are scattered across the island with his straw hats in disarray.
Luffy is ready to fight, but Jinbei has something else in mind.
on the next wood piece the kingdom in shock an order to execute neptune issued i'm gonna be king
of the pirates